When is a door not a door?
Sorry?
She doesn't understand.
Well. it's a riddle.
I think she understands
perfectly.
So I'll ask one more time.
When is a door not a door?
When it's "ajar."
Like one of those.
The jar I'm looking for
has a special symbol on it.
a triskelion.
three spirals connected.
We don't know what
you're talking about.
Maybe you should leave.
Oh.
It's a very special jar.
actually.
It was made from the wood
of a sacred tree
and used to capture
a dark Kitsune...
A trickster spirit
called Nogitsune.
Well. all these jars
contain are teas and spices.
So whatever it is you
came here looking for...
You know exactly what I came
here looking for. Mr. Dunbar.
You all do.
Hikari!
No!
You don't know
what you're doing!
I've been searching
for this for years.
I know precisely what I'm doing.
You can't control it.
I don't want to.
Set me free.
Not until you make me a promise.
What fool would ask a promise
from a trickster spirit?
Call it a mutually
beneficial arrangement.
If you're as all powerful and
omniscient as they say.
Then you already know
what I want.
You want retribution
against him.
his friends.
and everyone he loves.
Set me free
and we'll play a new game.
a game of chaos.
strife.
and pain!
You said it wouldn't bite.
I said it wouldn't bite me.
But that's also
because I wouldn't
put my hand in front of
the mouth of a frightened dog.
Thanks for the advice.
You got any idea how we're going
to get it out of there?
I have someone coming
who has a special talent
for these kinds of things.
He runs the animal shelter
next to my clinic.
Trust me. he's highly qualified.
We even have a nickname for him.
Oh yeah? What?
We call him "The Alpha."
The girl climbed out.
tried to pull it out.
lost her footing.
and ended up falling in too.
Is that all you got?
No protective gear?
No gloves?
I don't get bit.
Even if I did. I usually
heal pretty fast.
Well. even so...
No! He's gonna bite!
Hey there.
My name is Scott.
I'm going to help
get you guys out of here.
Scott. hurry! Come on!
Get out of there!
All right. climb onto me.
Climb onto me.
Come on. Alicia.
I got you.
That was close.
Hey. Alicia? You guys?
Let's go see the paramedics. OK?
What do you guys call him again?
The Alpha.
Right. like a dog.
No. like a wolf.
Good boy.
OK. Come here. buddy.
Do you know why
Cooper bit the lieutenant?
Because he was scared?
He was scared for you.
It's one of the best parts
about dogs. they fight for us.
Remember. the same way that we
see them as part of our family.
they see us
as part of their pack.
There's still time.
Oh. I know.
Yeah. I'll have kids
one of these days.
after I find someone.
or someone finds me. I guess.
Yeah. I meant there's still
time to beat traffic.
But if you want to talk.
there's still time for that too.
I think I was just.
maybe feeling kind of. uh...
Wistful.
It means a kind of
longing or regret.
a sort of melancholy
about the past
and the choices we've made.
Wistful.
Why don't you lock up?
I'll get my stuff.
I didn't see him.
I took my eyes off the road
for. like. two seconds!
Quiet!
Oh! Jesus!
Hey.
Shit. dude.
You know you could just
use the front door. right?
I never use the front door.
Especially when it's not safe.
Who says it's not safe?
You're seeing her too.
I mean. I've dreamt about her.
You know. now and then
over the years
I've had images flicker in front
of my eyes like blurry photos.
And then. two weeks ago.
something changed.
Those random images
flickering through
my head got clearer.
I saw flashes of her crying out.
silently screaming in pain.
in agony.
She was suffering.
Allison.
But I started seeing her face
more and more.
And then I started
hearing her voice.
And I can hear somebody
whispering to me.
Whispering what?
One word. and only one.
I hear it every time I go to
sleep and every time I wake up.
and I only wake up
from nightmares.
What word?
Bardo.
Uh. I... I. uh...
I was on the phone the other day
and I was writing down
a client's number.
But instead of the number.
I wrote that.
Scott. do you know
what bardo is?
A state between life and death.
You and I.
we're both seeing her.
We're both speaking
the same word.
It's not just a dream.
Allison is caught between
life and death.
It's not that simple.
Bardo is a Tibetan word.
It's a means of
interpreting death
and the movements
of consciousness
between physical states
of being.
It's just a word.
It's a concept.
Well. that fucking concept
is waking me up
in the middle of the night
in a cold sweat.
telling me my daughter
is still out there!
She can't be.
I mean. she...
She died in my arms.
I felt her slip away from me.
I know we all die.
I'm not pretending to know
what happens next.
But if there was something
after this life. some next step.
I don't think she made it.
And I think she's trying to
tell us she never crossed over.
It's been 15 years.
Let's say we accept all this.
What can we actually do to help?
There's a... a...
A ritual of some kind.
I know a few details.
I got a feeling the real answers
are in Beacon Hills.
OK.
What else can you say
for certain?
It has to be done by
the next full moon.
And if it's not.
we don't get another chance.
I'm not sure.
And I'll admit.
I'm a little scared.
We're talking about
dangerous rituals.
thousands of years old.
There are going to
be repercussions.
So can somebody
just say one thing?
Are we doing this or not?
Well. the message
was for you. Scott.
It's yours to answer.
It's more than a message.
This is the sword
that killed her.
Her blood
stained the blade.
I haven't been to Beacon Hills
in a long time.
None of us have.
But if you drive out tomorrow.
I can meet you there
by afternoon.
We're gonna need more help.
And more answers.
Yeah. I'm gonna need to find
some old friends.
Sound energy...
I'm speaking specifically
of the sounds that fill
our acoustic environment.
Our current ability to harness
those sounds.
as not only
a renewable energy source.
but as a green sustainable
electric energy.
Lydia. I hate to
interrupt you. especially
since you're going full throttle
with this tech shit
that none of us really seem
to understand.
Thanks for the input. Rick.
and for not interrupting.
- Yeah. Lyd. listen...
- Continuing on.
research into energy harvesting.
up until now...
Lydia. I just have one tiny.
little question.
Lyd...
Stop calling me Lyd.
- Lydia!
- Rick.
For someone who hates
to interrupt.
you seem oddly compelled
to keep doing it.
Look. all I want to know is.
who's Allison?
Lyd.
♪ We walk the streets ♪
♪ In tattered armies ♪
♪ We got the lion in our heart ♪
♪ We're not looking
for trouble ♪
♪ Just for some fun ♪
♪ But we're all ready
if you wanna start ♪
♪ So just remember.
the kids are back ♪
♪ The kids are back ♪
♪ Oh. watch out ♪
♪ Well. can you blame us ♪
♪ For living our dreams? ♪
♪ Just look around
and you'll see why ♪
♪ The kids are back ♪
Um. hey. Sheriff?
I really hate to bother you.
I just got a phone call
from Deputy Parrish.
He wants to talk to our...
consultant.
Another incident
at the auto shop?
His son definitely has
an unhealthy fixation
on that Jeep.
Do you want me to tell him?
Nah.
He better hear it from me.
You were right.
It wasn't gasoline.
Whoever set this fire used
a chemical accelerant.
Four fires in two weeks.
That's a serial arsonist.
Do I need to call in the FBI?
Well. maybe you should be
calling your son.
Trust me. right now Stiles
has his own fires
to put out.
I think we can handle
one arsonist.
The only thing I'd say is.
this one seems to have a plan.
You need to get that?
- Yeah.
- No.
It... it can... it can wait.
Mm-hmm.
- You want me to answer it?
- No.
Why do I have a feeling
that that's about me?
Or maybe my son?
He still seems pretty intent
on leaving high school
with a grand theft auto charge.
He took the Jeep again.
didn't he?
Why the hell does he keep
taking the Jeep?
Because he knows I hate it.
What the...
I'm not paying for those.
Oh. yes. you are.
What's up. guys?
I... I can't...
I can't take your pain.
That's because it doesn't hurt.
Hey. thanks for coming so fast.
Yeah.
Hey.
Do you really think
all this is true?
Allison being stuck.
unable to cross over?
I don't know.
But if being here and doing
this thing actually helps her.
and no one else gets hurt.
I'm up for trying.
OK.
Then let's try.
We need a handful of earth from
the ground where Allison died.
- OK.
What's next?
Anybody mind if
we close this thing?
Yeah.
Does your. uh.
mom know that you're here?
Does she know that you're here?
No.
And I kind of want to
keep it that way.
Yeah. me too.
All right.
Lydia. we've got the earth
where she died.
the weapon that took her life.
According to you.
that's steps one and two.
What is next?
I was. uh. hoping you could
help me figure that out.
I mean. to be honest.
I'm a little out of practice
with all of this.
You still scream like
a banshee. right?
Not quite like I used to.
It's just like a muscle.
You stop using it.
and it atrophies.
Why did you stop
using your power?
Stiles.
Obviously it has something
to do with Stiles.
Why is Jackson here?
What are you doing?
Well. firstly.
Jackson prefers not
to be talked about
like he's not in the room.
Second. well. Lydia called.
begging me to help. as usual.
And I said. OK.
so long as she promised
never to tell Ethan.
because I promised Ethan
that I would never
come back to this nightmare
hellscape of a town.
Thank you.
Oh. I love these games.
This isn't a game.
I have claws that
drip paralytic venom.
and a tail that'll
snap your neck.
So take your hand
off of me. old man.
Oh.
It's a tree.
It's not just a tree.
It's the Sacred Grove.
The ancients Druids
call it a nemeton.
Well. it looks like a tree.
All right.
Can we just...
Can we just stop
before either of us
does anything
completely embarrassing?
I think that qualifies
as pretty embarrassing.
It was coming loose anyway.
Are you gonna punish me or not?
Cause otherwise.
I'll just go to my room.
Eli. I don't...
I don't want to punish you.
I'd like to maybe understand
what you think you were doing.
I needed a ride to meet
my friends after the game.
What is wrong with that?
You're 15.
you don't have a license.
and it's called
breaking the law.
You never broke the law?
OK. You know what?
If this is about
the other thing.
then let's talk about
I don't want to talk to you
about anything.
I wouldn't push it
if it wasn't a thing.
But we both know
it's not just anything.
and now it's
definitely something.
I don't even know what
you're talking about.
Are you listening to yourself?
You sound drunk.
I can't get drunk.
You know that.
- It's not my problem.
- Eli. it's a thing!
OK. to you. not me.
I can teach you.
What if I don't want to learn?
Well. you're gonna
have to learn.
It's who you are.
You're a Hale.
I'll change my name.
That won't change the fact
that you're a werewolf!
And what if I'm not?
Maybe that's why
I can't turn into one?
You know. what if I'm
the first ever Hale
not to turn into a werewolf?
To be honest.
it would probably make
life a little easier.
Yeah. for me?
Or you?
Definitely me.
You're trespassing.
You're naked.
You're not.
- ♪ I'm looking in the fire ♪
- Paula.
♪ Breathing even higher.
lost in my desire ♪
Better?
♪ See the way you hurt me ♪
♪ Maybe you could feel me ♪
♪ Why I want to hurt you back ♪
♪ The karma queen reigns ♪
Eli. come on out.
I was thinking we could
practice before the game.
You know. basketball was
really always more my thing.
But. uh. I think
I'm getting better.
Maybe you can show me
some tricks?
Or maybe not.
You're giving me
that look again.
- What look?
- The look.
What are you talking about?
There's no look.
- There's a look.
- What look?
The relationship look.
- Oh.
- Yeah. that look.
Did I say anything?
You said it with a look.
And I'm not changing my mind.
And I'm not asking you to.
OK.
But your look is.
All right.
But. since we're
talking about it...
Sorry.
I got to go.
What are you doing here?
Looking for answers.
And I'm wondering if you've made
any recent trips to Japan.
Oh. for the love of God.
Come on.
Oh! I missed you!
- I missed you too.
- No. you didn't.
OK. I wanted to.
Well. that I can believe.
- Hi.
It's good to see you.
It's kind of awkward to see you.
I know.
OK!
Let's go find a tree
in the woods.
Come on.
You said we need to find
this thing by nightfall.
I haven't been to Japan
in years.
Are you sure about that?
Positive.
How long has it been since
you were in Beacon Hills?
Because I seem to remember
you telling us that
you were going to stay
in Los Angeles.
I was. but I wanted to ask you
another question.
And it. um. it might
sound a little strange.
You walk into a room
that contains a match.
a kerosene lamp.
a candle. and a fireplace.
What would you light first?
The match.
You came all this way to
Beacon Hills to ask me that?
I do have another question.
What has to be broken
before it can be used?
An egg.
I'm tall when I'm young.
and I'm short when I'm old.
What am I?
A candle.
Do you want to talk
about that bullet.
or you want to keep
asking me children's riddles?
What month of the year
has 28 days?
All of them.
What has many keys...
Stop.
Stop talking.
What has many keys
yet opens no locks?
A piano.
What has many teeth
but cannot bite?
A comb.
What is always in front of you
but can never be seen?
The future.
The more of this there is.
the less you can see.
What is it?
Darkness. you motherfucker!
It's me.
Um. hey. we're still looking.
Just getting a little worried
about meeting up on time.
So just give me a call
or text. anything.
Mm.
OK.
Ah!
It's this way.
What is it?
Someone's following us.
They've been following us
pretty much the whole time.
Who?
Here. come here!
Wait. wait.
I wasn't doing anything!
Sorry!
Uh.
It is you.
Eli. Derek's son.
Wow. you've gotten really big.
Yeah. It's probably
because I was only three
the last time you saw me.
What are you doing out here?
I was kind of wondering what
you guys were doing out here.
Hiking.
Can't you tell?
It's a really nice night
for hiking.
I know what you're looking for.
The tree. right?
That huge stump's that's
like 20-feet wide?
You know how to find it?
Kind of.
I sleepwalk.
I don't know why.
But I've just been doing it
for the last few months.
I used to wake up
in the woods too.
After you were bit
by Peter. right?
Yeah. your dad tell you
a few stories?
Yeah. all of 'em.
What about the tree?
It's not far from here.
I knew we were going
the right way.
No. you were going
the wrong way.
It's that way.
We were circling back.
- Hm.
- Thank you.
Well. I can help you find it.
- Got it.
- Hey. come on.
What are you doing?
So aren't you the screamer?
Banshee.
Yeah. but banshees scream.
right?
Well. they wail if you want
to get technical. but yes.
So how loud can you scream?
Loud enough to create a burst
of acoustic energy
that could crush your skull.
Good to know.
There it is.
OK. OK.
So what should we do
about Argent?
Uh. I mean. I'm never
gonna get a signal now.
Even if he's texting me.
I wouldn't know.
Well. we're going to
have to do this now.
We can't wait for him.
It's his daughter.
You said it has to be tonight.
He would want us to do this
without him.
Don't you have something to do?
Yeah.
Yeah. I have a lacrosse game
to play.
Well. more like a lacrosse
game to show up to
since I. like.
I never get to play.
Oh! You want me to leave?
OK. Uh. I got it.
OK. well. I'll tell my dad
that I saw you guys?
No. don't.
Don't tell him anything.
This is kind of...
Personal.
All right. Don't worry.
I won't say anything.
All right.
Now what?
OK.
Why are you looking at me?
I didn't write the instructions.
Yeah. you did.
You literally wrote
the instructions.
Okay. you know what I mean.
Do you feel that?
Yeah.
What the hell?
Uh...
OK.
That was fun.
Um. you guys want to go
get something to eat now?
I know.
Hey. guys.
It's Allison.
She's alive.
This can't be real.
It can't be her.
She was cremated.
She looks pretty
un-cremated to me.
She's not just un-cremated.
She's literally been
reconstituted out of thin air.
So that wasn't in
the instructions?
I got a question.
What do we do when she wakes up?
If she wakes up.
We need some help.
Mom. we got a problem.
She looks just like Allison.
Why. Scott. does she look
exactly like Allison?
You really want to know?
Just get her inside.
OK.
Chaos!
Strife!
Pain!
Listen up!
Tonight's game
is not just a game.
This is a preamble
to what comes tomorrow.
an overture to a symphony
of victory!
This tournament
is everything I've dreamed of
my entire career
as a lacrosse coach.
And that trophy is
going right here. boys.
And I know none of you
will ruin it for me
by losing this game tonight!
Am I right?
All: Yes. Coach!
Oh.
It's just you.
Just me.
But I'm here. with him.
We can talk about it later.
I came to watch you play.
Well. prepare for
disappointment.
'cause if you didn't notice.
I never play.
I noticed. and I'm going to
talk to your coach about it.
Oh. God. no! No. no!
- Hey. Coach. can I have a word?
- Don't do that.
Eli.
you probably got the feeling
that I'm not actually here
to watch your game.
Yeah?
Kinda.
And that maybe I'm here to
give my good friend. your dad.
just a little support as
he deals with
his somewhat delinquent son.
Maybe.
But I'm not.
I'm here to warn you.
You steal that Jeep again.
I'm going to haul your ass
into a jail cell.
have you tried as an adult.
and watch you get sent
to the state penitentiary
for a minimum of 90 days.
Did he tell you to scare me?
Maybe.
Good luck with the game. Eli.
Yeah.
What do you think about my son
getting a little playing time
tonight?
I think that's a great idea.
You don't know who my son is.
do you?
I don't know who you are.
But you look pretty athletic.
so I'm guessing your son is too.
That's my son.
I was wrong.
Just give him five minutes
in the game.
Let him prove himself.
Three minutes if we're winning.
- Five minutes.
- OK.
You know what?
You drive a tough bargain.
Three it is!
Coach.
Four minutes!
Not a second longer.
What about four and 1/2?
I checked her vitals.
Everything's normal.
at least normal for a woman
who's been dead for 15 years.
Maybe we should cut her open
and then see
if she's normal inside.
Not exactly how medical
treatment works.
But thanks for the suggestion.
How do we know she's OK?
I mean. not just physically
but mentally?
How do we know this is Allison?
Hm? Really Allison?
We don't.
This wasn't exactly part
of the plan.
Maybe our first step is
simply talking with her.
Since she doesn't appear
to be injured.
we're probably OK
to try waking her up.
- Mom?
- Yeah.
I think she's awake.
Our sons are trained
to be soldiers.
daughters to be leaders.
Shapeshifter. lycan.
werewolf.
to me it's just
another dumb animal.
Allison.
Allison?
Where the hell does
she think she's going?
She's probably
slightly confused.
Supposed to be slightly dead.
Split up.
If you find her. yell.
OK.
Got her!
Ah.
Hey. Allison!
You OK?
Not me. man.
Shit.
Hey. Allison. wait!
Whoa!
Who are you?
It's me. It's Scott.
Scott who?
McCall.
Where's the alpha?
You mean?
Where's Derek Hale?
Wait!
Hey.
Allison. she's alive.
She's back.
She's not the only one.
Levchenko.
did you call the power company?
I just did.
They said everything
is fine on their end.
- Huh.
- Might be an
electrical issue here.
Sheriff. we got another problem
that you might want to handle
first.
If it's another fire.
I don't want to hear about it.
Of course I want
to hear about it!
Get the hell in here.
both of you!
20 minutes ago. two hikers
were headed down the trails
and they spotted smoke.
We've got another witness
who said
they passed by someone
wearing a heavy black coat.
but couldn't see his face
because of a hood.
OK.
Levchenko. you're with me.
Hewitt. you're with Parrish.
Let's go.
Is that a new uniform?
How'd you get in here?
The door was ajar.
Who are you?
Someone who knows you
better than you know yourself.
Hands up where I can see 'em!
You are kitsune.
but you don't know it.
Your brother. Ekaida.
he knew it.
but he never told you.
How do you know
about my brother?
The spirit in you. it's old.
It's drawn to Beacon Hills.
Don't come any closer!
The power.
it's like an armor
protecting you.
But it cannot protect you now!
Ah!
Ah. Oh!
Oh!
There it is.
I don't want your life.
little fox.
Oh. Ah.
But I do want your tail.
You have nine tails
that can summon nine Oni.
Now
give them to me!
- Scott.
- Yeah.
We don't know where she's
going or what she's doing.
Or how the hell she's alive.
Well. can we answer that
question after we find her?
That woman may look
like Allison.
but it doesn't mean
that she is Allison.
She didn't recognize me.
Me either.
But she saw me heal.
She knows what I am.
So she doesn't remember us but
she knows about werewolves.
It's frighteningly convenient
for a werewolf hunter
who just got brought back
to life.
She also knew how to kick ass.
specifically my ass.
Hold on.
When I told her
my last name was McCall.
she looked at me like she...
was expecting something else.
Hale.
But if the only thing
that she remembers right now
is that she hunts
and kills werewolves...
Then we need to find Derek.
I'm coming with you.
OK.
Allison.
Who are you?
A friend.
despite appearances.
A friend with a fondness for...
riddles.
I don't remember liking riddles.
Oh. you'll like this one.
What's another word
for the metal silver.
and also the name
of a legendary family
who hunts werewolves?
Argent.
Allison Argent.
Time to hunt.
Time to kill Scott McCall.
the werewolf
who destroyed your family.
I don't remember that name.
Oh. you will.
We will help you.
I don't fucking trust you.
You would trust your mother.
wouldn't you?
You're not my mother.
But aren't I precisely the voice
you need to hear right now?
No. my mother's dead.
No. No.
That's why I'm here.
Our side has suffered
so many losses.
Allison. you have to remember
Scott McCall. Derek Hale.
Those men.
those monsters have murdered
so many innocent people.
They have to be stopped.
What do you want me to do?
The betas make the alpha
stronger.
So I take out
the weakest members first?
Scott McCall has too many
allies right now.
So how do I get to him?
The Oni will clear a path.
They will clear the board
of the other pieces.
leaving you to concentrate
on a winning move.
What's the winning move?
In the game of Go.
we call it the divine move.
None of my texts
are going through.
I can't reach...
anyone.
Do you think that's connected?
Oh!
Someone was killed here.
Yeah. I'm pretty sure
a lot of people
have been killed here. Lydia.
Recently.
Are we gonna be killed here?
Please tell me that
Allison didn't do that.
Dad. put me down!
Please put me down.
You said you couldn't walk.
I can hop.
Ow.
You almost had that shot.
No. I didn't.
Yes. you did. I saw it.
You were right at the goal.
You're better than
you think you are.
I was in for less than a minute.
I got the ball for a second
and I got knocked on my ass
and I twisted my ankle.
It wasn't anything.
Eli.
It was nothing.
It was something.
I was watching Coach
and he saw it too.
You're good.
You're really good.
And... if you can heal.
you can play tomorrow night.
and you can help them win.
The first step to transforming
is healing.
but you've got to be
willing to learn.
Ah.
Get down!
Run! Run!
Allison?
Ah!
Liam?
Oh. shit.
Scott. get to Eli.
Derek. he's not here.
He was.
He knows what to do.
We... we have a plan.
He has the...
He has the car.
Don't... don't try to talk.
Eli. he'll go to the shop.
He knows what to do.
Don't talk.
Hey. hey!
- Scott.
- What?
It's not just Allison.
- It's the Oni. It's Nogitsune.
- They're coming.
Scott. what do we do?
Liam. get to Stilinski.
find Lydia.
and tell them
we need their help.
Tell them we need everyone.
Malia. let's get him
out of here.
It looks like the radius
is about the same
as the previous fires.
Take the others
and see if you can find
any kind of incendiary device.
Parrish.
What's your take on this?
Are you asking me
as a deputy or?
As someone who's known to
set himself on fire
because he's a demon called
a hellhound?
Yeah. but I'm a nice demon.
Given.
Who set these fires?
- Not an arsonist.
- Yeah.
A serial arsonist would want
to watch the fire burn.
not have it snuffed out
minutes after ignition.
And plus they typically have
an emotional cooling off period.
and...
These are being set
one after another.
And all that says one thing.
that these fires...
Are not about fire.
Go see what you can dig up.
I'm gonna call our consultant.
I know that sound.
Parrish!
Hewitt!
Oh. God damn it.
I knew I should've retired.
Jeez!
Eli! Eli.
We're gonna find him.
But we have to help you first.
No. No. Eli.
His ankle. he twisted it.
He can't run.
But he can heal.
- No. he won't.
- Eli can't heal.
not like a werewolf. not yet.
What's wrong with him?
You know how some people
pass out when they see a needle?
Eli passes out when
he sees his own fangs.
He passes out?
- The fangs come out.
- He's on the floor.
Claws too.
Scott. you have to find him.
You have to find him before
she does.
Sheriff!
Where are you?
Mason?
Mason. help.
Help.
Ah!
Sheriff.
No!
Aw. shit.
Go!
All right. Come on.
Easy.
Here.
Easy. Easy.
You have to find Eli.
Eli.
Derek. you're gonna need to
let Scott and the others
take care of it. OK?
Anyone that loses
this much blood.
human or werewolf.
you're not gonna be any good
to anyone else.
We need a lighter.
The healing process
works faster with fire.
I've been known to light
a spark or two in my time.
Peter. no.
Do I need to remind you people
that he slashed my throat once
and it killed me?
When it comes to you.
most of us try to forget.
That is no way to speak
to your father.
Look. we're running out of time.
We've got to catch up to Eli.
You mean before Allison does.
Allison Argent.
back from the dead.
running around.
shooting up werewolves
like a good little hunter?
You must be so proud.
Can we just lower the level
of the testosterone
in the room. fellas? Huh?
Derek said that they had a plan
for when something like this
happens.
The auto shop.
That's where they'll go.
Emergency rendezvous point.
How far behind was Allison?
- Not far enough.
- I'm coming with you.
No. You need to find Lydia.
Liam and Hikari are already
looking for Stilinski.
but honestly. if there's anyone
who could figure
this thing out. it's Lydia.
Find Lydia.
I'll get Eli.
- Wait.
- I gotta go.
Wait!
Scott. wait. wait.
What. Mom? What?
If there's some small chance
that it's her.
that it's really Allison...
It can't be. right?
It's impossible.
Listen to me.
If I've learned anything
living in Beacon Hills.
it's that every time someone
says something's impossible.
somehow the impossible
seems to happen.
If you think it's really her.
you have to find her
and stop her
and help her remember
who she was.
- I love you. Mom.
- I love you too.
Go get her.
Come on.
What do you smell?
Fear.
That would be me.
You're gonna want to see this.
He was a kitsune.
probably didn't even know it.
If the Nogitsune murdered him.
then he did it
to steal his tails.
The tails only get him
one thing:
the Oni.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
I have a tail.
No one's planning on
stealing my tail. right?
Will you please shut up?
There's more going on and
I think it's all connected.
More what?
Well. someone's
been setting fires.
If Allison catches up to Eli.
we might need
some real medical attention.
not just a blow torch.
I feel like that
was aimed at me.
Get out of the way or
there'll be a gun aimed at you.
Of course.
Just satisfy my curiosity
about one thing.
Who are you going out there
to help.
her or him. predator or prey?
I'll stop anyone who tries to
kill an innocent 15-year-old.
And yet you look like
a man with doubts.
Let's ask the expert.
Mr. Deaton?
The Nogitsune is
an extraordinarily
powerful creature.
It can create illusions
that are nearly
indistinguishable from reality.
Illusion.
But that illusion today.
that looked pretty damn real
to me.
Me too.
I know what I saw.
I saw an exact replica.
meant to trick us
into lowering our guard.
My daughter is gone.
Whoever or whatever is out there
isn't Allison.
It's an illusion.
Then I say.
let's dispel the illusion.
Allison. stop!
Come on! Come on!
Go. go. go. go!
Ah!
Oh. shit.
OK. Go.
Oh! Ah. come on!
Come on! Let's go!
OK. OK.
I know you don't
remember everything.
but if you stop trying to
kill us for half a second.
I could help you remember!
Come on! All right! Hey!
We're gonna have to run.
I need you to heal.
I can't.
I can't heal. I can't transform.
I can't do any of it.
Well. you're gonna learn
right now.
How?
Like this.
We've got multiple calls
about a fire.
Copy. Dispatch.
We're en route now.
Parrish. go to two.
I'll hit the station.
But. Sheriff.
Mason. he just... he vanished.
We don't know
what happened to him yet.
Right now.
I need you at the station.
I'll check Hale Auto.
You copy me?
Copy. sir.
Come on. Eli! Don't stop!
She's right behind us.
Come on. keep going.
Kid. come on. get up. get up!
Go. go. go! Right there. go!
Listen. you're gonna have to
keep going on without me.
Wait. what are you
talking about?
I have to try to
get through to her.
She's trying to get
an arrow through you.
What is that?
Wolfsbane.
She coated the arrowheads
in wolfsbane.
My dad told me you almost
had to cut his arm off once
because of wolfsbane poisoning.
You need to run. Eli.
We're not far from the road.
I... I'll keep her busy.
I can't. OK?
I can't do it without you.
Hey. you're gonna be
all right. OK?
Remember. you just learned
how to heal.
You did that for me.
I gave you a push.
And if Allison has any chance
of remembering who she is.
she's gonna need the same push.
Find your dad.
I think I'm gonna need his help.
Yeah. OK.
Yeah. the fires all happened
right after the jar
was taken from Japan.
Liam. that's him.
That's the guy
who stole the jar.
the one who freed the Nogitsune.
He's the one setting the fires.
And not the Nogitsune?
Why don't we catch him
and kill the Nogitsune?
That sounds like
a pretty good plan to me.
Well. the Nogitsune's
not a person.
It's an ancient power. so old
it's practically elemental.
It might not be possible
to kill him.
Well. I'm willing
to give it a shot.
We're wasting time.
You guys can figure out
who's starting the fire.
We need to find Scott.
She drove this one.
smashed right into Derek's.
You smell something else?
Anger.
The air. it's rife
with a homicidal rage.
She certainly has the anger
of an Argent.
Then it's more proof
it's not Allison.
My daughter wouldn't kill
a 15-year-old boy.
You had the Nogitsune
in your head.
Maybe it's in hers.
If there's room enough.
with all of that
unadulterated fury.
Not everybody has your anger.
Not everyone has your optimism.
Don't underestimate anger.
Melissa.
We all have the same instinct
for fight or flight.
Flight begins with fear
but fight is born of anger.
She put an arrow into his truck.
They're on the run. that way.
Can you track 'em
through the woods?
Both: Yes.
Allison. stop!
I want to talk.
Sure. let's talk.
Dad? Dad?
Eli?
Eli!
You're safe. Eli.
You're safe.
Yeah. but Scott isn't.
Hey. we got a problem.
Three of them.
It was done by a sword.
Hikari!
Dad!
Oh. no!
Deaton!
Dad...
Remember who you are.
- Malia?
- Come on. Come on!
Allison. if you just
give me one second.
I can tell you the truth.
You killed half my family.
I never killed anyone.
and neither did you.
I know those daggers
have wolfsbane on them.
And I know you think you're
gonna go through with it.
Because that's what
the Nogitsune wants.
He wants me to die
in your arms this time.
Are you ready for that?
Because it's not easy.
Come on.
Eli. what are you doing?
- I can do this.
- Oh. shit!
No!
Eli.
Whoa. OK. stop!
What's it gonna take to
get you to stop and listen?
OK. you killed me.
Now can we talk?
Why is the guy who went to
Japan to free the Nogitsune
now in Beacon Hills trying
to burn down the woods?
He's not trying to
burn down the woods.
It's... only part of it.
Do we have to play
junior detectives?
Can't we just leave it up
to the actual detectives?
Do you see any actual
detectives standing around?
But what do detectives do.
anyway?
Do they. like. go to
the scene of the crime and...
detect something?
That's exactly what they do.
We need to look at
one of the burn sites.
the first one.
Guys. guys.
Hi.
We got a big-ass problem.
Derek. Stilinski. Eli. Deaton.
they're all gone.
What do you mean gone?
They were taken.
By who?
The Oni.
There's blood...
all around here. and a lot.
If she managed to cut him
with her ring dagger
then he's in trouble.
They're laced with wolfsbane.
How long does he have?
Six. eight hours at most.
These rapid burns...
There is something
systematic about it.
Is she gonna keep
talking like this?
I stopped listening
six hours ago.
All right. I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna spend
the rest of the day
walking through the woods.
trying to catch a pyromaniac.
Do you have a better plan?
We already know
what kills the Oni.
Silver.
You with me?
Go.
Get all the silver you can.
And if you find the Oni.
don't fight them. kill them.
We're heading back to
the main road. aren't we?
And my blood.
it's going to lure them.
I'm the bait for
the trap. right?
'Cause by the time the others
catch up to us. I'll be dead.
and you can pick the others
off one by one.
Is that the plan?
Yeah. actually.
That is the plan.
You don't hunt werewolves.
Allison.
And no matter what the Nogitsune
put into your head.
you don't kill them either.
And I think part of you
knows it.
I saw it the moment
you stabbed me.
Saw what?
Regret.
Go.
Jackson. what do you smell?
Ugh. The horrifying
stench of death.
What else do you smell?
It's not gas.
It's not lighter fluid
or anything like that.
It's different.
Chemical accelerant.
Mm-hmm. It's a quick burn
so they can't set
the rest of the forest on fire.
Well. does that tell us
anything useful?
Well. in terms of the fire.
they know chemicals.
They know exactly
how to use them.
I don't get it.
Why would someone
spend all this time and energy
burning up rowan trees?
- Rowan trees?
- Yeah.
That's what the smell is. right?
Jackson. do you know
what rowan trees become
after they're burned?
Ash?
Mountain ash.
You're not gonna kill me.
That's right. The wolfsbane is
going to kill you.
You had a code.
Mm-hmm.
"We hunt those who hunt us."
No.
You came up with a new one.
"We protect..."
"We protect those who...
cannot protect themselves."
You remember.
We should grab whatever we can.
I'm taking this.
Don't worry.
It's not the look.
It's more of a...
"you look really hot holding
a tactical tomahawk" look.
If we don't die tonight.
we can talk about it.
Huh.
Then I'm definitely not
dying tonight.
Scott.
Yes. he's handsome.
History is replete
with handsome killers.
He's still a killer.
What am I even doing here?
This... this can't be
the right thing to do.
Don't get lost in useless
moral quandaries. Allison.
Stick to the plan.
Your father is on his way here
right now.
I saw him at the hospital.
That was him.
No. he's on his way and
he's bringing Peter Hale.
You remember what
that monster did to Kate?
He ripped her throat out
with his claws.
He'll do the same to you
if he gets the chance.
Don't you remember
how they burned us?
We lost years.
Can't you feel that life
stolen from you?
I don't know what I feel!
A few more hours
and the sun goes down.
We'll take care
of everything then.
They come out at night.
- Who?
- The Oni.
And with them comes chaos.
Eli.
Eli. can you hear me?
We're not dead.
Not yet.
Where are we?
It's just an illusion.
What about them?
If we don't come up with a way
to get this wolfsbane out soon.
I'm going to die.
We need to find Liam.
Your beta?
My friend.
Liam and Hikari.
She's a kitsune.
That's why that arrow
didn't do anything to her.
Because of the fox.
It protects her. like armor.
It won't protect her
from the Oni.
Nothing protected you either.
- What do you mean?
- You died in my arms.
And if you let me.
I could prove it to you.
You're lying.
Just give me a chance.
If you still
don't believe me. fine.
Let me die.
And what if I do?
Well. then you're gonna
have to save me.
Derek. I'm not so sure
even your strength
could break those bonds.
not here.
Eli. are you OK?
How's your leg?
Yeah. it's fine.
It's healed.
You learn how to heal?
Yeah. kind of.
Well. Scott did most of it.
That's amazing!
Hey. Derek.
Maybe you want to be
a little more subtle
with your antics.
The Nogitsune isn't gonna
kill us. not yet.
He put us here to watch him win.
We're here for our pain.
Do you guys hear that?
It sounds like...
Lacrosse.
At least we know
she hasn't caught him yet.
No. she's caught him.
Allison knows to retrieve
her arrows whenever she can.
This was left so we're
following the right trail.
Guys.
I don't think
we're following a trail.
We're being led into a trap.
and I think that's it.
It's the college stadium.
That's where the lacrosse
tournament's being held.
And while they play
a lacrosse game.
we'll be playing right
into the Nogitsune's game.
That's where he'll make
his final moves.
Let's just hope he hasn't
figured out a divine move.
What's that?
It's a move in the game of Go.
It's a move so brilliant.
so inspired.
that it changes the shape
of the entire game.
A move that only a god
could make.
Divine.
I think the accelerant
used to start these fires
might be the same one used to
start a fire over 20 years ago.
Are you talking about the fire
that killed Derek's family?
And there's one more thing.
The person who came up with this
formula is supposed to be dead.
"Supposed to be dead"
is starting to be
a recurring theme around here.
Just... hold on.
Please.
It's my license.
It was at the ice rink.
The other pictures
didn't come out
so I tore that one off for you.
After you died.
your father gave that to me.
Lydia was there.
And Stiles.
Remember the winter formal?
I went with my friends.
Jackson and Lydia.
I don't remember anybody else.
I was there.
And I found you inside.
and we danced.
I don't remember any of that.
We kissed.
And that was the first time
I told you that I loved you.
Why did you do that?
Because I love you.
When you broke up with me.
I said I knew we were
gonna be together.
And you told me...
"There's no such thing as fate."
Do you remember what
I told you back?
"There's no such thing
as a werewolf."
Tell me the rest.
I can't. because I'm going
to die if you don't help me.
What do I have to do?
Wolfsbane only responds to fire.
You've got to burn it out.
A man looks at a photograph
of another man.
He says. "Brothers and sisters
have I none.
But this man's father
is my father's son."
Who is the man
in the photograph?
My son.
Ah.
Don't be afraid.
Oh. of this guy? No. no way.
Oh. my God. he's touching me.
The son of Derek Hale.
But not a wolf yet. is he?
When night falls.
he may earn his fangs.
his claws.
watching the rest of you die!
Whoa. uh...
you couldn't find a lighter?
Do you want to live or not?
Burn it out.
Eli. did you see that?
Did you see your eyes?
How the hell am I supposed
to see my eyes?
They're the things I use to see.
- They were glowing.
- What?
They were?
Yes.
Oh.
Wait. don't!
Tell me. Eli.
do you like riddles?
I'm more of a limerick
kind of guy.
You know. I like the rhyming.
Finstock. thanks for
reminding everyone here
that no team chokes
quite like Beacon Hills.
We're still up. Hogan.
Shit!
I need to find my father.
If he's here.
he's in danger too.
Allison. wait.
Look. this isn't
just about us anymore.
I think I remember you.
or maybe someone like you.
maybe someone
I was in love with.
And maybe...
Maybe if I had more time.
I would remember everything.
But I can't help you right now.
I have to find my father.
I think he might be
the only one I have left.
Yeah.
Let's put one of the players
back in the game.
No!
Allison.
Hey! Allison. Allison.
They don't know that it's you.
Not even your own father.
So just...
be careful.
I just tried to kill you.
and you're telling me
to be careful.
Why would you do that?
Because I'm still in love
with you.
Eli!
Where the hell
did you come from?
Get off the... hey!
Off the field!
Get off the field! Look at you!
Eli?
It's happening now.
The mountain ash is more
than a barrier.
It's a gateway between
his world and ours.
Oh. I really hate when you
say shit like that.
Isn't it just ash?
Parrish has to break
the barrier.
He's the only one
that can do it.
Jackson.
OK. so it's a place.
but it's not real.
They're all there with my dad.
and they're alive.
This part of the game?
It's like he's knocking
pieces off the board.
So how come he put me
back on it?
I don't know. but I need to
get you out of here.
Come on.
Oh! What the hell was that?
Mountain ash.
It's him.
It's really him.
It's him who?
Adrian Harris.
He kind of looks like
our chemistry teacher.
I was your chemistry teacher.
Jackson.
you fucking imbecile.
Do it. Scream. Lydia.
Scream like a banshee.
Oh. Oh. that's right.
You haven't screamed in years.
have you?
What do you want from us?
Well. I don't want an apology.
seeing as how
you ruined my life.
and you served me up
as a human sacrifice
to some demented druid.
I was in London for all of that.
The sun's going down.
If the Oni come out at night...
There's 10.000 people
in this stadium.
What are we supposed to do?
Come on.
Hey. Coach?
- Come on.
- Coach!
Coach. hey!
Oh. no. no. no. no.
Unacceptable.
You graduated. McCall.
You're not ruining this for me.
Coach. every single person
in this stadium is in danger.
Is there any way to get them out
without panicking them?
Yeah. you win the game.
What happens if they tie it up?
Sudden death.
Coach.
there's gonna be
10.000 sudden deaths
if we don't stop this game.
Crap!
I haven't felt this level
of disappointment
since I lost my virginity.
You want to help us win. McCall?
Here.
Four minutes.
whoever scores first wins.
Number 11?
That used to be my number.
Do you want it back?
No. no. That's OK.
Just. if you're gonna wear
my number. you better score.
I'll try.
Let's go! Let's do it!
Asses on the field!
We score first!
Come take a look. Lydia.
This was no small
accomplishment.
This illusion has
several layers.
Here. Lydia.
let me show you one.
You want me to watch
a lacrosse game?
No. no.
I want you to watch
your friends die.
Come on.
Take a look through
the microscope.
You didn't change.
What?
When they took Eli.
you didn't change.
He means you didn't transform
in front of your son.
I haven't.
He hasn't seen me like that.
Not since the first time.
OK. what was the first time?
I don't know
if he'd even remembers.
He might have been too young.
Coyotes had come into the house.
They clawed through
the screen door.
Eli was playing on the floor.
and they were heading
straight for him.
I transformed instantly.
Roared so loud it shook
the entire house.
Coyotes took off
and there was Eli.
looking up at me.
He was shaking.
He was...
He was terrified.
And he wouldn't let me
come near him for days.
That look of fear in his eyes
when he saw me.
I couldn't get it
out of my head.
That's why he can't change.
I think every time
he starts to. or...
maybe every time he tries.
he must see my face...
snarling back at him.
Get it to McCall! To McCall!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Whoa. Sh...
I knew the Nogitsune
was too chaotic
to play this game on his own.
He needed me to help him win.
All I had to do was
give him my pain.
Thanks to you and Scott McCall.
I have plenty.
We all have pain.
But Lydia's pain is
particularly appealing
to a thousand-year-old demon.
My pain isn't anything to him.
On the contrary. heartbreak
is a veritable delicacy
to the Nogitsune.
So give him a taste. Lydia.
Tell us why you left Stiles.
Give us your pain.
or the next time.
I shoot Jackson in the head.
No. Lydia.
Lydia. don't do it.
Don't do it!
I left.
I left because of a dream.
What happened in the dream?
My eyes open...
And I see broken glass.
It's from a windshield.
And I'm crawling
on the pavement.
I'm trying to reach Stiles.
There was a crash.
We'd been thrown from the car.
Except he's not moving.
He wasn't blinking.
He wasn't breathing.
Lydia. it was just a dream.
Until it happened again.
And again.
Becomes this recurring dream
until I can't tell anymore
that if it's a dream...
Or a premonition.
If I was never in
the car with him.
there wouldn't have to be
a crash.
And he wouldn't have to die.
And you wouldn't have to scream.
Banshees don't scream.
They wail.
New plan.
You take the shot.
I'll cover you.
- Are you kidding?
- No. it's your shot!
Come on.
Where did this kid come from?
Is he even in high school?
That's one of my best students.
He looks like he's 30.
Who the hell is that?
That's Greenberg.
What do you hear?
It's like the game's happening
right next to us.
I can hear it too.
I think my son's on the field.
Yes! Take it!
Eli. take it to the rack!
Whoo!
Yes!
Holy shit!
Scott. did you see that?
Did you me score?
My dad was actually right.
I'm actually pretty good.
Oh. my God. my dad.
This isn't over.
We're gonna find the others.
Come on.
Peter! Wait!
No! No!
No more illusions.
Where's Scott? Where's my son?
He's on the field.
He's trying to save everyone.
He's playing the game.
That most definitely
sounds like your son.
But as for your daughter...
I forgot to tell you
something. Peter.
The arrow wasn't the only thing
Allison left behind.
Wolfsbane.
You think I wouldn't recognize
my own daughter?
It is you.
I don't know.
I don't know who or what I am.
But my friends are in trouble
and it's all my fault.
No.
Dad. what's that?
Allison?
The real tournament begins.
Where are we?
We're in his world.
This is it.
They're here.
They're all trapped here.
So are we.
Something's happening.
I think it already happened.
I've killed Oni before.
Then let's kill a few more.
You can burn through this.
right?
You've done it before.
That was years ago.
The amount of power
this is gonna take.
I don't know if I can do it.
OK. What do you need?
You need a pep talk?
One of those "you can do this"
speeches?
I don't do speeches.
I don't do pep talks.
I'm not here to boost your ego.
And I'm not gonna be
your cheerleader.
So whatever you need to do
to get your shit together.
you gotta do this for yourself
and you gotta do this right now.
You are a hellhound
that burns hellfire.
Now burn this fucker up!
We can't get loose.
Dad.
Parrish. we need to
buy him more time.
Go ahead. Lydia.
Watch your friends suffer.
Look out!
Fight. Allison. Come on.
She'll hear you.
Mountain ash doesn't work
on banshees.
Allison is alive.
Your best friend is alive.
and she's out there
fighting for her life.
Don't lose her again.
She'll hear you.
Lydia. she'll hear you.
Allison!
I remember.
I remember everything.
We're not done yet.
The game is mine.
Take me.
Let the others go.
All the lives here belong to me.
All you need is me.
Scott. don't do this.
Allison kills me.
I die in her arms.
the same way that
she died in mine.
That's the move that wins
the game. isn't it?
I've already won.
You lose!
Until I'm off the board!
And I'm still standing.
And I'm still the alpha.
An arrow to the heart
to save everyone else?
All the other players
go free.
No.
No. I can't.
I... I can't...
I cannot... no.
No.
Kill him. Allison.
and I win the game.
Allison. please.
Don't make me watch
my friends and my family die.
Game is mine!
Kill him!
Something tells me
this isn't over.
I certainly hope not.
Scream all you want. Lydia.
- No!
- The game is over.
The wolves howl to
signal their position...
To the rest of the pack.
Tell me. Scott McCall.
what is the sound
of the wolf who is ready to die?
I'd tell you.
but I'm not ready to die.
Fox fire.
What is that?
Silver. you motherfucker.
Come on. come on.
OK. Stop. Stop.
The only way we can
break the bonds
is with our strength combined.
you and me.
What strength?
I don't have any strength.
Your will as a wolf.
We do it together.
You're my son.
You're a Hale.
A werewolf.
Go!
Mason! Sheriff!
No!
Do you remember. Scott.
the gift that you gave me?
The bite of the alpha.
the power of the werewolf.
Derek. it's not real.
It's just another illusion.
Dad?
Eli?
Eli. can you hear me?
Yeah.
Yeah. I can hear you.
Eli!
Harris had his chance.
Now it's my turn.
my revenge.
I'm going to kill them all.
starting with this child
right here.
You wanna kill someone.
start with me!
We can't fight him alone.
He's too strong.
We have to break the illusion.
We have to catch him.
You can't catch me.
You can't kill me.
You can't even find me.
You're right.
We can't find you...
but we can find each other.
A wolf howls to signal its pack.
What about a werewolf?
A werewolf roars.
Hey. hold him!
We gotta hold him!
You can't!
You'll both burn up with him!
- Scott!
- What?
You're the alpha.
He's part of your pack now.
Parrish!
Light this fucker up.
Dad?
Here. let me help you.
- Hikari!
- Liam!
♪ Tell me. love ♪
♪ Tell me from the start ♪
♪ How we came so far
then you fell into the dark ♪
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪ If you need me be the one
to wrap your arms around ♪
♪ Lonely is the night time ♪
♪ Lonely is the night ♪
♪ Satellite. satellite ♪
- Lydia.
- Allison!
♪ Bring me home ♪
♪ Satellite. satellite ♪
♪ Cause I feel you
around me always ♪
♪ I feel you around me always ♪
♪ I feel you around me always.
looking down ♪
♪ You're around me always ♪
♪ Satellite. satellite ♪
The first night
I met Derek Hale.
he saved my life.
Then he said we were brothers.
and I thought that he was crazy.
But no. No. he was right.
Eli. from that moment on.
we were brothers.
And. uh...
Derek Hale was the first person
to teach me that
you don't just get the family
that you were born with.
You get the family
that you find.
You know. I'm not sure
how your dad would feel
about me giving you the Jeep.
But. um. something tells me
it's the right thing to do.
He hated that Jeep.
After my son left it behind.
Derek towed it in. thinking it
was probably beyond repair.
But then he opened up the hood
and he pulled off
all the duct tape
Stiles had stuck on it.
And he managed to fix it.
That Jeep.
no matter
what's been done to it.
it just keeps running.
He could never figure out
why it wouldn't break down
and stay down.
And I don't think
he ever realized that
that's exactly
the way we saw him.
I have never seen anyone
take the kind of punishment
that Derek Hale took...
And kept taking...
In order to protect
the people he loved.
He kept standing back up...
Until the day he couldn't.
Hey.
Your dad had complicated
feelings about that Jeep.
But it doesn't mean it needs
to be complicated for you.
All you got to do...
is keep it running.
Just keep it going.
♪ We are victims
of the night ♪
♪ We are victims of the night ♪
Don't get too attached.
We got adoptions on Saturday.
Eventually him.
I know you're gonna be tempted.
but not a lot of treats.
He's still growing dog.
- Oh. really?
- Yeah.
He's pretty heavy already.
When he's ready.
Hi.
I have this feeling.
It's like.
all this time has passed
and I want to figure out
how to get it back.
Like. I'm happy for everything
that's ahead of me.
but I... I just...
I feel this kind of regret.
you know?
I think...
I think I feel...
Wistful.
Yeah. that's exactly it.
Do you feel that way?
No.
I'm not worried about the past.
because now I have a future.
With him.
And you.
OK. quiet.
Why did we stop?
Hey. I thought... I thought
I was gonna go see my lawyer.
Hey.
Hey!
Hey. hey. hey!
Hey.
Hey!
Who the hell are you?
Whoa. whoa. hey!
No. hey!
What's... what's going on?
Get your hands off me!
Hey. come on!
Get your hands off...
Good evening. Mr. Harris.
There's been a change of plans.
It's been decided that
you'll be placed at
a far more suitable
detention facility.
What kind of facility?
The Eichen.
I think you'll be
very comfortable there.
No. no. no. no. no. no.
No. God! No. no. no! No!
No! It's some kind of mistake!
No! I'm a high school teacher!
Come on. the kids.
the teenagers.
they're werewolves!
Trust me.
We've heard plenty of stories
about teenage werewolves.
There's always a new one.
Remember who you are.
♪ Standing on the ledge ♪
♪ I'm thinking now. man.
I want jump down ♪
♪ Somebody's shouting from the.
the ground. the ground ♪
♪ Sucking on a lemon.
Will I ever get to heaven? ♪
♪ Will they ever let me in
if I. I try. I try ♪
♪ I'm burning off
my fingertips ♪
♪ It's never enough ♪
♪ I don't know
what to make of this ♪
♪ So I'll lock it up ♪
♪ Whoo! Yeah! ♪
♪ I'm burning off
my fingertips ♪
♪ It's never enough ♪
♪ I don't know
what to make of this ♪
♪ So I'll ♪
♪ Run into the hills
to get away ♪
♪ Bad luck ♪
♪ Still. I can't help but love
the taste. yeah ♪
♪ I'm running through
the graveyard ♪
♪ They never save a place
for me. yeah ♪
♪ And I'm doing well ♪
♪ Standing on the ledge
I'm thinking ♪
♪ Man. I really wanna
jump down ♪
♪ Somebody's shouting from the ♪
♪ The ground. the ground ♪
♪ Sucking on a lemon.
will I ever get to heaven? ♪
♪ Will they ever let me in
if I... ♪
♪ Whoa! ♪